

Harshad Banadar **Business Analyst and Consultant**

Email: harshadbanadar@gmail.com Mobile(+91)9960-8282-15 Pune, Maharashtra, IND.

Summary

I am self-motivated, versatile, creative professional with a record of increased responsibility with Technical and Managerial skill set. Proficient in prioritizing and completing tasks in a timely manner (with in KPI and SLA), yet flexible to multitask when necessary. Customer focused with industry experience including Consulting, Business Analytics, PMO, BusinessOperations, Change Management, Incident Management, Marketing Branding, MIS_Reporting SDLC and ERP Implementation and its Transition. Currently working o RPA and IoT projects.

Career History

Total Experience – 4.10 years

Business Analyst & Consultant Fujitsu consulting India Pvt.Ltd

Aug 2015 - Present (Pune)

Market Research Analyst Unimak softwares Pvt.Ltd Internship -MBA

May 2014 - Jul 2014 (3 Months)

Skynet Info Services, Kolhapur. May 2011 -Aug 2012 (16 Months)

Hardware Engineer & Technical consultant

Skills & Expertise

- ITIL V3 Foundation Certified
- Cloud Computing Certified (CloudF)
- **Project Co-ordination**
- **Business Operations**
- ITIL Change Management
- **Incident Management**
- ERP implementation
- Agile ,Scrum
- MS Office, MS Project, SQL
- Consulting & Requirement Gathering
- Handling the overseas clients issues in appropriate manner
- Marketing- Branding, Pre-sales, PR
- Client Visits & Event Management

TOOLS

- TeamCenter10
- Service Now
- Power BI
- Salesforce
- MS Visio
- HP-SM7
- Fujitsu Service reporting tool
- JIRA
- Citrix, Tera Term
- UI path
- Tableau

Professional Experience

Fujitsu Consulting India Pvt.Ltd

Projects-

1-MITSUI & CO-SAP SUPPORT Client of Fujitsu UK

Aug. 2015 - April 2017

70 people Team

Role- Business Analyst and Consultant

Work Responsibilities:

- Gather business requirements such as scope, processes, alternatives, and risks
- Analyze client's business requirements and processes through document analysis, interviews, workshops and workflow analysis.
- Conduct 5+ levels of testing including functional, regression, user acceptance, integration, and Performance to verify the client's needs are met
- Communicate client's business requirements and change requirements by constructing easy- to-understand data and process flow
- Identify and resolve any business issues for the client including questions on business processes, system configuration and monitoring the dedicated project tasks and activates
- worked on SAP domain for BASIS and FICO Module
- Interacts directly with clients for support in appropriate manner and track the client data via (Tools, Emails and Call) EMEA and US region
- Update existing documentation, SOP, creates and track KT plans, Maintain Master database, RFC's, tracking and resolve the incidents
- Owner of weekly client meetings and status call and presenting the documentations as per Requirements

1.1 HR4U (Events, Employee engagement Committee Fujitsu)

Working for Multiple Events for employee engagements 2015- Present

Work Responsibilities:

- Organizing and managing corporate level events and cultural activates.
- Promotion activities for the events, campaigning
- Branding for the Products and Services
- Planning, Budgeting, Coordinating and Organizing
- Co-ordinate with other management team, Stakeholders and Vender management
- RFC's Documentation, Presentation and Reporting
- Market and Trend research

1.2 NISSAN -AMO

Fujitsu Japan NISSAN Team

May. 2017 – Present

24 people Team

Role - Business Analyst and functional Consultant

Work Responsibilities:

- Engage client to gather software /product requirements and ensure alignment with development teams
- Translate stakeholder requirements into over tangible deliverables such as functional specifications, user cases, workflow/process diagrams, data flow/data model diagrams.
- Evaluate risks related to requirements implementation, Application support and project communications.
- Coordinate with stakeholders, client and team for day to day activities
- Draft and maintain business requirements and align them with functional and System requirements
- DATA transition between NISSAN to RENAULT
- Change and Incident Management with in SLA
- End user Support as per the requirement and Ticket Management
- Co-ordinate with other management team and client for Transition/Customizations of the new process/Task
- System Administration, ID creation and Modification, Providing access on servers
- Identify and resolve any business issues for the client including questions on business processes, system
- Prepare and Maintain Daily Task, Weekly and Monthly Activity reports and Status calls*
- Working with e-HUB and CAE team for Task and Resource management (Rosters, leaves)
- Handle the CAE server request and user utilization request.
- Generate and resolve the Ticket (Service Now)/incident
- Working as a PMO and Project coordinator

2. Unimak softwares Pvt.Ltd (internship)

Part of 1 implementation Project June 2014 – Jul 2014

Role- Market Research Analyst for ERP products

Work Responsibilities

- Primary and secondary research in SME segment
- Gathering the client requirement.
- Intermediate between Development team and client.
- Implementation for ERP products and customize the requirement as per client.
- Proposal creation as per requirement. Pre-sales, Branding and Marketing

3. Skynet Info Services

May 2011- August 2012

9 People Team

Role -Hardware Engineer & Technical Consultant

Work Responsibilities:

- Counseling the Clients regarding their requirements for systems
- Assembling Computers (Systems)
- Installing applications & Operating Systems (Windows /Mac/Linux)
- Fault-finding and troubleshooting
- Hardware & Networking (LAN, WAN)
- Setup the Database
- Assigning the jobs to respective person
- Cross selling, up selling
- Assigning the jobs to respective teams
- Assets/Procurement management

Education

Master of Business Administration 2015 SIT, Pune University
Marketing Management (full time) First Class (62.57%)

Post-Graduation Diploma in Foreign Trade 2014 Pune University

P.G.D.F.T First Class (68.5%)

Bachelor of Engineering, 2013 D.Y.Patil college of Engg.Shivaji University

Information Technology First Class (62.57%)

Diploma, 2009 Dr. D. Y. Patil Polytechnic, MSBTE

Computer Engineering First Class (64.08%)

S.S.C. 2003 Maharashtra Board Second Class (56.66%)

Personal Details

Name-Harshad Nandkumar Banadar

Nationality-Indian

Address-Sr no 3/3 Flat no AB102 Padmalay Park, Wing B Building A, Punawale Corner, Ravet PCMC-411033

DOB- 15th January, 1988

Gender-Male

Languages Known- English, Hindi, Marathi Japanese (Beginner)

Interests- Dance, fitness, gadgets, parties (coordination and attend)

Place – Pune

Harshad

Harshad Banadar